It was the perfect score. But hell was their reward.
The Pale Door is a horror, western film directed by Aaron B. Koontz.
The Dalton gang escape to a nearby town after a train robbery goes south, but they are met
by a coven of witches with sinister plans for the unsuspecting outlaws.
Truman, played by Noah Segan.
Maria, played by Melora Walters.
Duncan, played by Zachary Knighton.
Lester, played by Stan Shaw.
Dodd, played by Bill Sage.
Cotton Mather, played by James Landry Hébert.
The Pale Door is a 2020 American horror Western film directed by Aaron B.
Koontz and written by Cameron Burns, Keith Lansdale, and Koontz, with Joe R.
Lansdale as executive producer.
It stars Devin Druid, Zachary Knighton, Melora Walters, Bill Sage, Pat
Healy, Stan Shaw, Natasha Bassett, Noah Segan, and Tina Parker.
The film explores themes of witch, brothel, church, cowboy, train robbery.
The tone is dark.